制暴: 無限殺機
- Boss. This for you.  - No, no, no. Come on.
- 老闆 這是給你的  - 不 別這樣
I can't impose on your family.
我不能麻煩你的家人
No.
不行
Yasmin, she made this just for you.
雅斯敏特意為你做的
Jefe, please.
老闆 請收下
Take it.
拿著吧
Tell her thank you.
替我謝謝她
Yeah.
好
So, listen.
聽著
Today's gonna be hard.
今天會很辛苦
We got inspections all day.
全天都有檢查
Forms to build, forms to break down
要填表 拆表
and deliveries all gettin' in our way.
還有送貨的來添亂
We work hard today,
今天努力幹活
there'll be a bonus for ya.
還會有獎金拿
And let's all go home
咱們都得完好無損
with the same amount of fingers that we came with.
回家 一根手指都不能少
All right.
好吧
Hermanos.
兄弟們
Have a good day. Let's get it.
祝今天順利 開工吧
- Morning, Jess.  - Buenos dias, Levon.
- 早啊 潔茜  - 早 萊文
- How you doing?  - I'm good.
- 你怎麼樣?  - 挺好的
- Gracias.  - Hey, Levon.
- 謝謝  - 嘿 萊文
No one's been asking you for money today?
今天沒人跟你要錢吧?
No.
沒有
- Why?  - Because, apparently,
- 怎麼了?  - 因為很顯然
I am the only person in the family
全家只有我
who can do the vendor accounting.
會做供應商賬目
Oh, excuse me!
真是抱歉
Hey, I guess we're evil parents, babe, huh?
嘿 看來咱倆是邪惡父母啊 親愛的?
'Cause we make her work a couple hours.
就因為我們要她幹兩小時活
Not today.
今天不行
How about you get those disbursements done, huh?
先把那些款項支付搞定如何?
We got a line of trucks out there that need paying.
外面一堆卡車等著結賬呢
You could pay me.
你可以先付我
Pay you for what?
付你什麼錢?
For 19 years of free rent,
付我19年的免費房租
and groceries, and high school,
食品雜貨 中學
college, makeup, karate classes?
大學 化妝品 空手道課?
- You want me to keep goin'?  - Really? No. It's okay.
- 要我繼續列舉嗎?  - 認真的? 不用了
Levon, can you sign that, please?
萊文 能籤個字嗎?
- Dad?  - What?
- 爸?  - 幹嘛?
- Today is a total shitshow.  - I know.
- 今天簡直一團糟  - 我知道
And you scheduled three things at once.
你還同時安排了三件事
She's not wrong.
她說得沒錯
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia and Family Construction.
嗨 這裏是加西亞家族建築公司
Yeah, you're speaking with Carla,
我是卡拉
you've had me on hold for a bit now.
你們讓我等了好久
So, we're gettin' those deliveries today, right?
今天能送貨對吧?
Yeah, I'll hold.
好 我等著
This is what I need for tonight.
這是今晚要用的
That's insane. What is that? Is that for your wedding or something?
瘋了吧? 這是什麼? 你結婚啊?
No, it's for tonight.
不 就今晚用
We finished the semester, so we're gonna celebrate.
學期結束了 我們要慶祝
I mean, you just finished one semester.
你纔剛結束一個學期
- Right. It's a big milestone.  - Is it?
- 對 這是重要里程碑  - 是嗎?
- Yes.  - Is that a thing?
- 是啊  - 有這說法?
Look, it could be worse, okay?
聽著 情況可能更糟
- Look, I'm passing the hat.  - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- 我在籌錢  - 嗯
- That gets us a party van.  - Oh, my God.
- 夠租派對巴士了  - 天啊
Locks in a private room for dinner.
還能訂餐廳包間
Just saving like crazy.
拼命省錢呢
Yeah. I just need a card on file.
對 只需要一張信用卡擔保
Mija, I can't. I don't...
女兒 我做不到...
Mija...
女兒...
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
好吧 算了 我不要了
Just give her what she wants.
她要什麼就給她吧
No, Mom, I can fight my own battles.
不 媽 我能自己爭取
Oh, no, no, nobody's arguing that.
噢 不 沒人質疑這點
I mean, everybody needs a party bus, right?
誰不需要派對巴士呢?
After they finish one semester. Here.
尤其是剛結束一學期的時候 給
Thank you.
謝謝
Hey, Kate.
嘿 凱特
Excuse me.
借過
He needs to get back to work.
他得回去幹活了
Get the fuck out of here. It's not your business.
滾你媽的 關你屁事
I'm good, boss.
我沒事 老闆
All good. Five minutes.
沒事 五分鐘就好
Hey!
喂
I was respectful.
我很禮貌了
You weren't.
你可沒有
Get outta here. Get up.
滾出去 起來
Don't come back.
別再來了
- Vamonos.  - Vamonos.
- 走吧  - 走
You okay?
你沒事吧?
How did you do that?
你怎麼做到的?
We need to get back to work.
該回去幹活了
This one. Over to the right.
這個 搬到右邊
- You got it.  - Thanks, Kate.
- 明白  - 謝了 凱特
Levon! Holy fuck!
萊文 臥槽
Was that some military shit?
那是軍隊的招式嗎?
You didn't see anything.
你什麼都沒看到
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
要是爸知道 他會氣瘋的
Can you teach me?
能教我嗎?
Look, my grandpa, he was a paratrooper.
我爺爺是傘兵
Taught me how to break fingers,
他教我怎麼掰斷手指
track animals.
追蹤動物
Break fingers?
掰斷手指?
Yeah.
對
Grandma made you tinga. Shredded chicken.
奶奶給你做了廷加燉雞
It's good.
很好吃
And Grandma made you some handmade grandma tortillas.
還有奶奶手工做的玉米餅
Why is everyone always feeding me?
為啥總有人給我送吃的?
If we don't, you'll just eat canned tuna and peanut butter.
不給你送 你就只吃金槍魚罐頭和花生醬
You didn't see anything, okay?
你什麼都沒看到 懂嗎?
Snitches get stitches.
告密者沒有好下場
Just get my back if I ever need it.
我需要時你得罩著我
Sure, Jenny.
沒問題 珍妮
See ya.
回見
Love you, Daddy.
愛你 爸爸
Love you, too, honey. Get in the truck.
我也愛你 寶貝 上車吧
What's the occasion?
什麼大日子?
No occasion.
沒什麼
Meredith's entertaining some friends.
梅雷迪思要招待朋友
Yeah.
是啊
I didn't realize today was your visitation.
我不知道今天是你探視日
You could let her stay.
你可以讓她留下
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth, we don't have to do this.
是 求你了 羅斯醫生 沒必要這樣
You weren't there when her mother needed you
她媽媽需要你時你不在
and you won't be there when Meredith needs you,
梅雷迪思需要你時你也不會在
but I will.
但我會
Oh, I know.
噢 我知道
You want to strike me.
你想打我
It's your only answer.
你只會這一招
Violence.
暴力
You're an unsafe parent.
你是個不合格的父親
You're a killer.
你是殺人犯
You can't pretend that you're not.
別假裝你不是
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
失陪了 羅斯醫生
Today's my day.
今天是我的日子
Why's your grandfather throwing a party on my day?
你外公為什麼在我探視日開派對?
I'm super hungry. I didn't eat.
我餓死了 還沒吃飯
I was waiting for you.
在等你呢
You were?
真的?
Yeah.
嗯
Okay. Let's go.
好 走吧
- Here you go.  - Thank you.
- 給  - 謝謝
- Thank you.  - Enjoy.
- 謝謝  - 慢用
I don't need you buying stuff.
不用你給我買東西
Come on. Open it.
來嘛 開啟看看
It's Mama.
是媽媽
I took that picture
這張照片是我
with a film camera my dad gave me.
用我爸給的膠捲相機拍的
Grandpa took all of Mama's pictures down.
外公把媽媽的照片都收起來了
Sometimes I forget what she looks like.
有時候我都快忘了她的樣子
She looks like you.
你跟她很像
Dad, can I tell you something?
爸 我能跟你說件事嗎?
Anything.
什麼都可以
I'm mad at Mama.
我生媽媽的氣
For dying and leaving us.
她丟下我們走了
It's okay.
沒關係
I hurt, too.
我也很難過
Matt will see you now.
馬特現在可以見你
He's throwing parties for her during my visitation time.
他在我的探視時間給她辦派對
Staring at me, laughing.
盯著我 嘲笑我
He's baiting you.
他在激怒你
Hoping you throw a punch.
就等你揮拳
Nah.
不會的
Then he wins.
那他就得逞了
Opposing counsel
對方律師稱
alleges you have untreated PTSD
你因服役而患有
and brain trauma from your military service,
創傷後應激障礙和腦部創傷
making you at-risk for violence.
因此有暴力風險
I served Britain, the country of my birth, for 22 years.
我為出生地英國效力22年
I'm the fuckin' bad guy for it?
反倒成壞人了?
It gets worse.
更糟的還在後面
They're requesting supervised visits
他們要求探視需監督
and a reduction in visitation from two hours a week
並從每週兩小時
to one hour every two.
減為每兩週一小時
I have to fight this.
我必須抗爭
I have ten grand saved up.
我攢了一萬塊
From sleeping in your truck?
睡卡車攢的?
Court won't be thrilled
法庭不會喜歡你
by your lack of a fixed residence.
居無定所
Hey, I'll figure it out.
嘿 我會解決的
Why does Doctor Roth hate you so much?
羅斯醫生為什麼這麼恨你?
He thinks I killed his daughter.
他覺得我害死了他女兒
Did you?
你有嗎?
It was suicide.
是自殺
I was overseas on a deployment.
我當時在海外部署
She battled depression her whole life.
她一生都在對抗抑鬱症
You've heard of attrition warfare?
知道消耗戰嗎?
Yeah. You grind the enemy down slowly.
知道 慢慢拖垮敵人
This guy's got a team
這傢伙有一隊
of thousand-dollar-an-hour attorneys
時薪千刀的律師
who will bleed you dry
會榨乾你
until you turn to dust and blow away.
直到你化為塵埃
The best we can do is negotiated surrender.
我們最多爭取談判投降
You have a daughter?
你有女兒嗎?
I got you guys a little somethin'.
給你們帶了點小東西
Nina.
尼娜
Jocelyn...
喬斯琳...
- Chantel. And Rubi.  - Thanks, Mama.
- 尚特爾 還有魯比  - 謝謝媽媽
Dude, these are insane!
老兄 這太絕了
Where'd you get these?
哪弄來的?
I have a cousin. Or seven.
我有幾個表親
Salud, bitches!
乾杯 混蛋們
Thank you.
謝謝
shots.
一口乾
Hey!
嘿
What? What? What?
幹嘛? 幹嘛?
What the fuck are we still doing here?
我們還他媽在這幹嘛?
He said he wants the One.
他說他要「那個」
"I want the One. I want the fucking One."
「我要那個 我他媽就要那個」
What the fuck does that mean?
這他媽什麼意思?
He'll know it when he sees her, okay?
他看到就會知道 懂?
Do you know how much fuckin' money
你知道這單能賺
we're gonna make on this?
多少錢嗎?
- We better.  - Enjoy, yeah?
- 最好如此  - 享受吧
Hey, last establishment.
嘿 最後一站了
You guys have early flights.
你們早班機
Is that back table open?
後面那張桌空著嗎?
It's yours if you tell me your name.
告訴我名字就給你
It's Jenny.
我叫珍妮
Hi, I'm Johnny.
嗨 我是喬尼
Hi, Johnny.
嗨 喬尼
Right here.
這邊
My man.
老兄
You are more than a pitch deck.
你比提案精彩多了
Nina?
尼娜?
- Nina, don't throw up.  - I'm fine.
- 尼娜 別吐  - 我沒事
She's making her puke face.
她要吐了
- Let's get you to a bathroom.  - Oh, ew.
- 帶她去洗手間  - 嘔
Cheap! Bad energy.
廉價 晦氣
Ew!
嘔
Oh, my God.
天啊
I hate you so much right now, it's not funny.
我現在恨死你了 一點不好笑
It's kinda funny.
有點好笑
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
天 我妝都花了
I cannot go out there like this.
這樣沒法見人
Okay, well, pick your battles, 'cause we're leavin' in 30.
好吧 取捨一下吧 30分鐘後出發
Fuck!
媽的
Go.
走
Jenny's missing.
珍妮失蹤了
What do you mean, "missing"?
怎麼「失蹤」了?
She went out with her friends on Friday.
她週五和朋友出去後就沒回來
Saturday, we were worried,
週六 我們急了
so we called the cops, and then on Sunday...
就報了警 週日...
She had a piano recital on Sunday
她週日晚上有鋼琴演奏會
We invited half our family.
我們請了半個家族的人
My cousin Dinora is a Police Captain in Philly,
我表姐迪諾拉是費城警長
and she says they don't work these cases.
她說警方不查這種案子
They take a report and forget about it.
錄個口供就不管了
Can you help us?
你能幫我們嗎?
I can keep the site running smoothly.
我可以維持工地正常運轉
No. Help us find Jen.
不 幫我們找珍
My dad was a Green Beret.
我爸是綠色貝雷帽
I can see you guys comin' a mile away.
我一眼就看出你的底細
You hunt bad guys.
你們專抓壞人
You jump outta planes.
你們從天而降
And you get those bad guys.
然後解決那些壞人
I'm a different person now.
我現在已經不同了
All right, well,
好吧
maybe this'll help her.
也許這個能幫到她
Here, it's 50.
給 這是5萬
Take it.
拿著
We have another 20 for expenses.
還有2萬經費
Come on, just take it, man.
拿著吧 老兄
I'm sorry.
抱歉
It's not who I am anymore.
我早就不做了
Gunny, it's me!
甘尼 是我
Don't kill me!
別殺我
I got steaks!
我帶了牛排
If you'd shot a foot to the left, I'd be dead.
你剛纔偏左一英尺我就死了
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
如果想殺你 你都死了
You know, for me,
知道嗎 對我而言
there's no separation between day and night.
晝夜沒有分別
So, I got to make my own.
所以我自己安排時間
It's hard livin' in a gray world.
活在灰暗的世界裏很難
I couldn't save your eyes.
我救不了你的眼睛
Sorry.
抱歉
That eats at me.
這事一直折磨我
No.
不
You saved my life.
你救了我的命
Joyce would be burying tags in the back yard
要不是你趕來救了我
if you hadn't come along, scooped me up and ran.
喬伊斯早在後院給我立墓碑了
What's her name?
她叫什麼名字?
Jenny.
珍妮
Jenny. All right.
珍妮 好吧
She a good kid?
她是個好孩子嗎?
She's a great kid.
她非常優秀
Now, you do this, you better lock in.
既然要做 就必須全力以赴
You better go full on, no half-measures.
不能半途而廢
But you do, God help 'em.
但只要你堅持到底 上帝會保佑他們
I told Jenny I had her back.
我答應過珍妮會保護她
Well, uh...
呃...
I miss ya.
我想你
I worry about ya,
我擔心你
but you didn't have to come down here and pretend that
但你也不必專程跑來來假裝
you needed my permission for something
需要我批准
you already made your mind up about.
你早已決定的事
Get in here. We're eating.
進來吧 吃飯
Hey, Carla.
嘿 卡拉
Thanks for coming.
謝謝你能來
Where is he?
他在哪?
Upstairs. First door on your left.
樓上 左邊第一間
"Moonlight Sonata".
「月光奏鳴曲」
-Yeah.  - It's beautiful.
- 對  - 很美
She turned down a music scholarship
她拒絕了音樂獎學金
to go to business school.
去讀了商學院
She wanted to be like her pops.
她想成為像她爸爸那樣的人
Be a big land developer.
當個大地產商
And she will.
她會的
Yeah.
嗯
Nah. No, thanks.
不了 謝謝
Your family needs hope.
你的家人需要希望
But I can't face 'em like this.
但我不能這樣面對他們
When my wife passed,
我妻子去世後
and I left the Royal Marines,
我離開皇家海軍陸戰隊時
a lot of people would've given up on me.
很多人都會放棄我
But you were patient with me.
但你對我很有耐心
- You, Carla, Jenny.  - Jenny.
- 你 卡拉 珍妮  - 珍妮
You're my family.
你們是我的家人
Look at me, brother.
看著我 兄弟
I'm gonna bring her home.
我會帶她回家
I promise.
我保證
I'm gonna bring her home.
我會帶她回家
尋人：珍妮·加西亞
"Skip's Bar."
「斯基普酒吧」
Thank you very much. Good, bro?
非常感謝 不錯吧 兄弟?
You good? Yeah?
還行嗎? 嗯?
How you doing?
你好嗎?
You need a little aperitif, you know?
你需要點餐前酒 懂嗎?
All right.
好吧
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
嘿 小子 走錯門了
Get the fuck out.
滾出去
Hello, Johnny.
你好啊 喬尼
Wanna have a race? See who wins?
想比誰更快嗎?
Hands up. Stand up.
舉手 站起來
Place your fingers behind your head.
雙手抱頭
You a cop?
你是條子?
You wish I was a cop.
你希望我是條子
Your adventure, kid.
你的冒險 小子
Wh